The Sorcerer Supreme.
Doctor Strange is a action, animation, fantasy film directed by Jay Oliva.
Stephen Strange embarks on a wondrous journey to the heights of a Tibetan mountain,
where he seeks healing at the feet of the mysterious Ancient One.
Doctor Strange (voice), played by Bryce Johnson.
Wong (voice), played by Paul Nakauchi.
Mordo (voice), played by Kevin Michael Richardson.
Ancient One (voice), played by Michael Yama.
Dr. Gina Atwater (voice), played by Susan Spano.
Dormammu (voice), played by Jonathan Adams.
Marvel Animated Features (MAF) is a series of eight American direct-to-video animated superhero films made by MLG
Productions, a joint venture between Marvel Studios (later Marvel Animation) and Lions Gate Entertainment.
The film explores themes of magic, mystic, cartoon, tibet, based on comic.
The tone is thought_provoking.